Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Top 200
minimum
casual
.
遥か未来へ 今駆け出したんだ
まだ見ぬ不安すら全て越えて
あの日描いた僕が僕であるために
見つぬけてページの続けが強
君と言う希望と言う
It's like a one page, like you and me.
Do you want to call me this?
It's incredibly crumbly and mealy,
and I'm not certain I've ever had something that dries the mouth so.
And yet it's tasty.
Good. I'm so glad to hear it.
Sister Lily, it seems you possess an exemplary talent for cooking.
I only prepared a few basic dishes.
There's more than enough for everyone.
Don't hesitate to eat as much as you'd like.
And the same goes for you two as well, of course.
Yes, thank you.
A noble of the Clover Kingdom,
and a ramshackle church eating dishes that defy identification.
Oh wow, it truly does dry one's mouth out.
Yes, quite extraordinary, isn't it?
Our good boys, Yuno and Asta, both sent home money from the first wages they received as Magic Knights.
Thanks to them, we were able to buy a huge supply of pot potatoes,
enough to make sure all the children here at the church will have full bellies every day.
Here's an idea. Maybe next time buy us something different for once.
There's no need to be greedy, Nash.
Just look at how big and strong Yuno here got on a steady diet of pot potatoes.
Yuno, sending the first of your wages back home, that was very honorable.
It's nothing.
That's not true.
We're very grateful, Yuno.
The money that you sent helped us out so much.
And not just with pot potatoes.
We were finally able to patch up all the holes in the floor.
We dug a well out in the garden, too.
Thank you for everything, Yuno!
Yeah, for everything!
Asta sent something, too?
Yes! And what a contribution it was!
How much did he send?
Oh, um… he… uh…
Beat you, Yuno!
When I get my wages next month, I'm sending it all to you.
What?
That really isn't necessary.
The amount you already sent was so generous.
We'll be more than fine for a while.
But thank you for offering.
You'll get it all.
Um… well… sure.
If that's what you want…
Pardon, Salim sir.
We really ought to be on our way now.
Why, what's the hurry?
We can stay a little longer, surely.
Just think, as members of the nobility,
we have a rare opportunity to broaden our horizons here.
Please, Sister Lily.
Might I trouble you for another glass of water?
Of course!
Looks like it's empty.
Well, I'll go.
Let me…
No, it's alright.
You just stay put and relax.
Wait, please.
Just a moment.
It still gets rather chilly out at night.
Thank you very much.
A real gentleman, aren't you?
Yes, well, you know.
These things just come naturally to me.
That's what it means to be a true nobleman.
What happened?
What was that crash?
Where's Sister Lily?
I recognize that.
The villains who killed her,
uh…
Uh…
What happened?!
What was that crash?!
Where's Sister Lily?!
I recognize that
The villains who came after Selim before were wearing these brooches
Those bandits who attacked us earlier?
I can't believe it
I gave her my robe so she wouldn't catch cold out here
But because she was wearing it, they took Sister Lily mistaking her for me
Oh, it makes sense
That must be what happened
Is Sister Lily going to be okay?
Is she? You know? You know?
Yes, don't worry
I'll bring her back
I'm going to
Yeah, so am I
Count me in
No
Everyone else stays here
I can handle this on my own
Hold on
Remember our mission
To protect Selim
We don't know when they'll come for him again
We must depart at once
You can't really mean that
What about Sister?
Yeah, come on, Four Eyes
What did you just call me?
Um, Four Eyes
I mean, Klaus
Can't we?
That's quite enough, Mimosa
Now, I know you're worried about your friend
But you will just have to leave it for the local watch to handle
We're leaving this instant
Come, I need everybody to move quickly
Let's go
Yes, sir
You know?
No, sir
You will do your duty
Insubordination will be punished
Be that as it may
I'm going after her
You know
Does whatever he pleases
Did no one ever tell you that recklessness isn't the same as bravery?
You know
He knows my name
How about I show you the difference?
Towering tornado
What's that?
That's one down
Four to go
I'm not necessarily gonna kill you
So don't worry
This might hurt just a little bit, though
Sorry
I see what's going on here
It's me you've been after this whole time
Not Salim
You really are a clever boy, aren't you?
Now I'll sit back and watch you drown
I don't know what you're talking about
I can breathe here just fine
What the?
If you want to know how to drown someone
Let me show you
That's two down
I can't believe you fell for our false trail so weaselly
How do you like that?
Not bad
Let's see
How about this?
Impossible
What is it about people like you?
You always seem to think that bigger is better
Fine, I'll just
Too late
Three down
Just two to go
That's sister Lily
Stop right there
That's a good boy
You wouldn't want to do anything stupid
And get the sister's pretty face burned now, would you?
You know
Even as young as you are, you seem to have a real talent for magic
If you ever see someone in trouble, please help them instead of looking the other way
Promise me
You too, Austin
What, sister Lily?
Did you say something?
Now then, down to business
And over that grimoire of yours, you know
Without it, you should be suitably helpless
What would you do with my grimoire?
Sell it, perhaps?
Maybe I'll decide to burn it instead
I'm not especially concerned about what becomes of it
If you don't have your grimoire, the magic knights won't see any reason to keep you around
Is that what you're after?
And if I won't give it up?
You're refusing?
That's what I thought
Hand it over
Then you can take your precious sister and be on your way
Not happening
What?
Don't you understand?
She'll be
I'm not going to let you hurt her
You think attacking me is going to do any good?
If you want to give it a shot, okay?
Sure
I won't be the one attacking
Who?
Right!
Steel creation magic!
Spiral lance!
Mimosa
Right!
She'll be okay
Are any of the bandits unaccounted for?
By my count, there should be one more of them
Ran away then
What were you planning on doing if I hadn't been there to help?
Why are you here?
Honestly, you know, do you take me for some kind of fool?
He does, the brat!
Now listen closely
As magic knights, we have a solemn duty
To safeguard the people
I already suspected something was off
This bunch wasn't out for Salim
They were after you
You imagine a noble would want to visit this village
That he'd eat pop potatoes and without complaint?
I'm sorry, but I don't think so
And they didn't abduct the sister thinking she was Salim
Rubbish
I found it strange that Salim would want you as his bodyguard after losing to you
After you left to rescue sister Lily
I used a spell on Salim
My plant creation magic, flower of truth
It's Yuno's fault that I didn't get to join the magic knights
Him and that four-leaf clover grimoire
Damn book!
I'm going to take it from him!
He'll know what real pain is by the time daddy gets through with him
I will have my revenge!
He gave up everything easily
But once you decided to come find me, how'd you know where to look?
That was Mimosa's doing as well
Plant creation magic
Magic flower guidepost
Let's see
Oh yes, there they are
And that's how we were able to arrive just in time to provide backup
I'm very glad you came
I needed the help
Thank you, Klaus
Mimosa
It's nothing
Quiet!
Honestly
Blaming others for your own failure?
Obviously you'd be the loser in a match against Yuno
He earned the approval of all the squad captains
Chief among them, Captain William Vongence
Leader of the Great Golden Dawn
That should tell you how talented he is
Thank you, sir
Yes
Well
Don't misunderstand me
You still have a ways to go before earning my approval
Right
Now then
I'll overlook your insubordination this time
It was all this cowardly little idiot's doing in the first place
What next?
Your choice
Shall we bring them to the capital?
Hmm
No
I don't think that will be necessary
Are you certain?
As long as they never come near Hodge village again
Those are our terms
Now make yourselves scarce
And never repeat this folly
Do you understand?
You stupid commoner
Making you lose your guard like this was all part of the plan
Huh?
Holy lightning rising Zalim
Water creation magic
Holy fist of love
Behave yourself
And try showing some remorse
That goes for you too
Yes, ma'am
I think perhaps we should consider recruiting her into the magic nights
Now
There's been a change of plans
We will be taking them in
But first
Tell me where the other one went
Now that's my idea of a good time
I was ready to step in if it looked like things were getting dicey
But they handled it just fine without me
William's new recruits are certainly nothing to be ashamed of
Not at all
How long were you planning to lay the belt?
Do you know how loud you are?
You need to return immediately
There is a mountain of work to be done
All right, all right
At this rate you're gonna give yourself an ulcer
And whose fault do you think that is?
You're really back
I'm so glad that you're okay
So glad, so glad
I guess we shouldn't be surprised
Not with magic nights on the case
Thank you all
Mimosa, Klaus
And lucky you two were there as well
Think nothing of it
We have the culprit, that cowardly fool
Honestly, what was he thinking?
Oh, right
Please help yourselves
The least that we can do is feed you before you go
They may be a bit cold, but you can have as much as you'd like
The flavor's not so bad, really
I thought magic nights weren't supposed to lie, sir
Hm
Perfect
A star?
The Wizard King has evaluated your deeds, and he has seen fit to grant you a star.
Thank you, Captain. We're honored to receive it.
Oh, wow. How many people can say they got a star on their very first mission?
Although, I don't recall doing anything that extraordinary.
On the contrary, Selim's testimony was quite valuable.
Thanks to that, Congressman Hapshats' wrongdoings have all come to light.
Bribery, fraudulent accounting, shadowy deals.
Everyone involved has been rounded up, and you get all the credit.
I wonder, sir, did you accept this mission, having anticipated such an outcome?
Evil deeds must not go unpunished in the Clover Kingdom. It is our duty to see to that.
Yes, sir.
Klaus, you know, Mimosa. I look forward to seeing what you will accomplish in the future.
Sir.
You know Mimosa. As far as new recruits go, well, they seem capable, I suppose.
I expect a great deal. Oh, yes. Especially from you, you know.
A star. Things turned out quite well in the end.
But, you know, don't ever go off on your own again.
Right.
Why did you pause? Come on, you know, look at me.
I want you to look me in the eye now and promise me that you won't do it again.
Sure.
You know? Hey, wait! You know!
What? The Golden Dawn got a star? I can't believe it!
Take us to your leader, Jubins.
Justin, we finally got down to a hundred star difference, too.
Well, it looks like we're back up to 101 now.
No way! We were totally catching up to them, too!
Yeah, we were close.
No, sir. Not even slightly close.
Really, our total's at negative 30.
Take us to your leader, Jubins.
Shut that thing up!
They won't be in the lead for long.
It's just 101 stars. We'll catch up soon!
I'm coming for you, Golden Dawn!
You know!
Sorry to interrupt, but there's urgent news, sir.
We have a situation on our hands, yes?
Calm down, Marks.
The timing couldn't be more perfect.
I know just who to give this mission to.
Who, sir?
Haha.
誰もここから出られない
閉じた狭い教室で
今日も主役が輝いた
僕は眩しくて目を閉じる
散々考えた革命は手の中に
おかしいだろう
笑いたければ笑えばいいから
残された僕らは
何かになりたくて
いつまでも
同じ朝を迎えてる
明日を選ぶのは
君自身しかいないよ
超えていこう
今日までの僕らを
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Clover Clips!
My Chariot.
Well, pretty impressive, is it not?
The whole thing is nothing less than a marvel of craftsmanship.
Pure perfection.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, its majesty practically screams Golden Dawn, don't you think?
Yeah.
Amazing!
What is this thing?
It's almost as awesome as the crazy cyclone!
I think it could even give HaHa's wicked shooting star a run for its money!
You'd better believe it.
I don't know who you are, strange boy, but thank you.
Are you leaving yet?
What? Clear out a dungeon?
Me, Asta, and Luck? It'll be fine.
I can handle one measly dungeon no problem.
Black Clover. Page 14. Dungeon.
My magic is never giving up.